噢  一个包裹
Ooh! A package.
等一下  里面是什 么 一件新衣服
Wait, what's in it? a new blouse?
一个新包包
A new bag?
还是那种短到都拉不过腰的性感内衣
Underwear that doesn't go all the way up to your waist?
这是个古董级的搓衣板
It is an antique washboard.
哦  真是个漂亮的玩意啊
Oh! isn't she a beaut?
它将会帮助
It's going to help
玛蒂和我赢得这个周末的杰瑟普拓荒者寻踪
Maddie and me win the mother-daughter challenge
母女挑战赛
At jessup's pioneer trail this weekend.
呃  不就是那个我以前
Ugh! is that that woodsy place
和玛蒂去郊游的那个
That Maddie and I used to go to on field trips
最大的特色在于上厕所的时候
Where the highlight was going to the bathroom
要坐在圆木上的深山老林么
While sitting on a log?
对头  玛蒂和我已经连续四年
Yep! Maddie and I have been doing this challenge
参加这个挑战赛了
For the last four years.
你只要在树林中搭帐篷
You camp in the woods
体验着和十九世纪先人们一样的生活
And live like people did in the 1800s.
你这是造了什么孽啊
Are you being punished?
其中最成功的母女组合
The most successful mother-daughter team
将会赢得金色的奶油搅拌器
Wins the golden butter churn
并且在其他的女同胞面前耀武扬威
And gets to lord it over the other ladies
整整一年
For the entire year.
只不过现在金搅子还是一幅照片
Yeah, this is just a picture
因为我和我妈并没赢过
'cause mom and I have never really won it.
对啊  我们中总有一个在拿够胜利点之前
Well, one of us always seems to get leprosy
被裁定为得了麻风病
Or fall into a wolverine nest
- 或是掉到了狼窝里头  - 对的
- before we get enough points. - yeah.
我们中的一个  指的是玛蒂
And by one of us, I mean maddie.
- 妈  - 怎么了
- mom. - hmm?
我可以看得到听得到你
I can see and hear you.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
呃  这不会是你又要拖着我去的
Ugh! this isn't going to be one of those things
那一堆破事吧
That you drag me to, is it?
我们笑个啥呢
Why are we laughing?
我跟着你去有什么好笑的
What's so funny about me going with you?
你到底要不要邀请我
Are you inviting me or not?
丽芙  这是脏兮兮苦哈哈的野外生存
Liv, this is rough-and-tumble outdoorsy living.
我们当然不会邀请你了
Of course we're not inviting you.
她胆敢不邀请我
How dare she not invite me.
当然了  这活动听起来
Sure, it sounds gross
又恶心又脏兮兮的又愚蠢
And dirty and stupid,
但是她好歹要问问我啊
But she should have at least asked.
这样我就可以严词拒绝
Then I could have turned her down
并且嘲笑她了
And laughed in her face.
算了吧  你一天都撑不过去的
No, you wouldn't survive a day.